nofeehost.com 2008-12-17

# Free Web Hosting Service, 100M free site space, FTP, ASP Hosting

|  |   
---  
|  |    
  
    _ **NoFeeHost Privacy Policy**_ This statement discloses the privacy practices for the NoFeeHost Website. 

NoFeeHost recognizes that our users have legitimate concerns about privacy. This privacy policy, which is part of our User Agreement, sets forth our practices regarding the collection and use of "personal information" as well as the choices we offer you regarding the use of this information. "Personal information" is information that personally identifies you, including, for example, your name, address, and email address. 

This policy only addresses our activities from our servers. Other sites (including those that we link to and third party sites or services which we co-brand) may have their own policies, which we do not control, and thus are not addressed by this policy. You provide certain personal information to us when you: (a) register for NoFeeHost.com, (b) sign up for special offers from selected third parties, (c) send email messages, submit forms or send other information to us. We may collect personal information from you at other points on our site that state that personal information is being collected. Our servers automatically collect information about which sites users visit and which pages are viewed within NoFeeHost Website. We use a feature of your browser called a "cookie" to assign a User ID that automatically identifies your computer when you visit the site. We also use cookies placed by third party servers to target the advertising delivered to you. This practice is common in Internet advertising.

We use personal information, among other things, to anticipate and resolve problems with your service, to personalize your service, to investigate activity that may violate our user agreement, and to develop and market products and services that may be of interest to you. If you indicate that you would like to receive information about products and services from third parties, we disclose your personal information to these parties. 

**Account Information.**  
You can review some of the personal account information you supplied to us by accessing member services. 

**Security.**  
We use industry-standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, such as firewalls and secure socket layers where appropriate. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. 

**Additional Privacy Protections for Children.**  
We require parental consent before allowing children under the age of 12 to access our Website. We also encourage children to seek the consent of their parents or guardians before providing any information about themselves to anyone on the Internet. Children should never reveal their addresses, phone numbers or other personal information to any strangers on the Internet. 

**Further information.**  
We cannot ensure that your private communications and other personal information will not be disclosed to third parties. By way of example, without limiting the foregoing, we may be forced to disclose information to the government under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or we might disclose your information to other sites as part of offering additional functionality to you. Additionally, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose your personal information to private entities, law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate. Therefore, we do not promise that your personal information or private communications will remain private.

You acknowledge that this privacy policy is part of our user agreement and you agree to be bound by all of its terms and conditions. 

|  |
